BGM
Here we go, Apkami!
This time we're joined by Reina Yokoyama of Morning Musume 24 and Rin Kono of Angulum!
In this program, we will be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
We will show you the process of recording, rehearsing, and more!
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at our two MCs.
First of all, I'm Yokoyama.
Yes, I'm Yokoyama.
I missed a rehearsal recently because I was feeling a little sick.
You don't often see rehearsal videos without you, do you?
That's right.
It's not so easy to watch the rehearsal without me.
So you are behind the other members.
So I check the rehearsal videos more for the next rehearsal.
At that time, if you check the rehearsal video
When you look back at the rehearsal video, you can see that the staff made the position of the audience in the rehearsal video vertically 1,000 to 1,000 meters from the position.
The staff had taped lines 1, 2, and 3 vertically from the position of the stage to make it easier to see the position of the stage.
Thanks to that, I was able to check the position very clearly.
That was great!
I felt that the space was really warm and welcoming.
It made me feel like I wanted to respond to the warmth of the space.
And I feel like I have to do my best in the rehearsals that follow.
I recently had an experience that made me feel more motivated to work hard in the rehearsals that follow.
What a wonderful story!
Yes, it is.
I recommend it to all the members.
It was a really good experience!
I, Kawada...
I have a similar story.
I also injured my foot.
I was the only one who was out of formation
I had to sit on the set and perform.
There was a time when I had to perform sitting on the set.
But at that time, the members
They cared about me and came up to me
and they came really close to me.
Because I was sitting there
I could see parts of them that I hadn't noticed before
I see things that I never noticed before.
I can see things that I've never noticed before.
I could see that this member was particular about this part.
or the way they look at the back when they sing
I felt how cool they were.
I felt their love for each other.
I was able to discover something new.
It's so nice.
I've been sitting on a chair for a little while at concerts since the beginning of this year.
I had a chance to sit on a chair for a little while at the concert
I also had a chance to sit on a chair for a little while at a concert
I had a neck injury at that time.
I had a neck injury at the time.
I sometimes felt a pain
I often felt pain from the slightest vibration.
But the members noticed that too.
around me, so I didn't jump as hard as I could.
It's amazing.
You can feel their love.
I hope we can continue to have good gigs in the future.
Rehearsals and all.
I'm going to do my best.
So, this time, I'd like to share with you the following information about Apkami.
First of all, let's start from here.
New Corner "Apkami Photo Gallery
The video of Apkami Photo Gallery, which we started last time, is now available.
The video of Apkami Photo Gallery, which we started last time, is now available!
Videos of Apkami Photo Studio started in the last issue are now available!
New Corner
This is the second part of the Apkami Photo Gallery!
Please take a look.
This is Ruri Dambara from JuiceJuice!
In this corner, we'll be discussing a certain topic with the members of Hello!
Project members to deepen our understanding of each other and get to know them better.
And at the end of the discussion, we'll write down the words that left a deep impression on this board and take pictures of them.
and take a picture of it and leave it behind.
In order to get into the world of the song, you can listen to other artists' songs and get hints from them.
and get hints from them.
The song changes so much with your face.
I'm trying to be serious.
I'm serious.
I hope you enjoy the video of Leg.
Then, Yumi, please choose a subject for the next question.
Okay, I'll choose the weather.
In terms of how you changed your singing style or how it all started...
The way I sing.
I have always had a throaty singing voice.
I used to sing with my throat tightened.
But when I met my current voice trainer
I became aware of the importance of singing from the stomach.
I had never been good at singing low voice.
But I changed the way I sing, and now I have a low, strong voice.
But I changed the way I sing and started to have a low, strong voice.
But I don't want to forget my original way of singing.
Some people have praised me for it.
I feel that the difference in the way I sing is also difficult for me.
In my mind
I want to change my voice color depending on the song or music.
I want to be able to produce various voices.
That's for sure.
There are some things that can't be changed, like the quality of your voice.
I want to expand my range and try to have a mixed voice.
You couldn't at first?
Not at all.
Yeah.
It's hard. Some days I can, some days I can't.
It depends on how I'm doing.
It depends on the tone.
So my voice sometimes changes a little bit depending on the condition.
But if you change the way you sing
the range of the music widens even more.
That's for sure.
The low part of the adrenaline pumping part...
Ah...
It's low, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I could hear it when we were recording, but when I was performing...
I get it.
It doesn't come out when you don't want it to.
Sometimes it doesn't come out.
But recently I've been working with my voicer to change the way I sing.
I've been singing more and more, and little by little, I've been able to increase my chances of getting a hit.
I see.
So...
I'm not sure...
Fans may notice that you've changed.
So, yes...
I want to work harder and harder.
It's true, it's true.
There's a lot of weather.
But the biggest thing after joining JuiceJuice was the graduation of the original members.
When all the original members graduated...
Well, the biggest thing was that the songs from the 5-member era featured the 5 original members, right?
That's right.
Most of the songs were sung by those five members.
So many wonderful songs were sung by all of them.
So many wonderful songs were allocated to these five members, and they were entrusted with various parts.
There was a time when I was entrusted with various parts.
At that time, I felt like I had been
I used to be able to sing solo parts that I was good at, or in the range that I was good at.
I was given solo parts that I was good at, or in the range that I was good at, or something like that, and I would jump around a little bit.
And then I'd get a solo part in a song, and then I'd get a solo part in a song.
I was able to do a lot of different parts all at once.
But then I started getting a lot of different parts all at once.
I had a lot of confidence.
I had confidence that I could do it because I had practiced so much.
I also had a feeling that I wanted to do my best in the song.
I wanted to do my best in the song.
I was given the responsibility, but I couldn't do it well, and I couldn't digest it.
But it wasn't something I could do right away, so I practiced a little bit at a time, and little by little I became able to do it by myself.
Little by little, I started to be able to do it by myself.
I would get really angry at myself for not being able to do it right away.
I felt like I was entrusted with the job, and I had a lot of feelings about it.
But the thoughts just got bigger and bigger.
The ideal of what I wanted to do became bigger and bigger.
But in reality, I didn't reach that level.
I wonder if it's a kind of depression I feel toward myself.
I really understand.
There was a time when I felt that I was not good enough, but now I'm facing a lot of music.
But now I'm facing a lot of music.
But now I'm facing a lot of songs.
I've been able to see the younger members working really hard and improving.
I've also been thinking about my position as Juice Juice, and I've been thinking about what I'm really good at.
I felt like everyone was making the most of my strengths and supporting each other
and supporting each other.
But it wasn't just a difficult time for me.
It was absolutely necessary for me.
I wonder why I am able to sing while thinking about various things now because of that time.
I think that period of time was great weather.
I sang "Sad Heaven" at the concert of Hello! Project concert this winter, I sang "Sad Heaven".
I've never done it before, so it's difficult for me.
You can't do it anymore.
I can't do it anymore. Rio Kitagawa of Morning Musume。
I felt like I was being left behind, and I was disappointed in myself for not being able to do it.
But I said to myself, "I can't do it if I don't try.
When I could shake myself off
I thought, "If I can't fulfill myself, I can't do it anymore.
Nakagawa also rented a studio and practiced.
But I thought I couldn't do it because I couldn't get along with him.
But because of that experience, now you don't want perfection, do you? On the contrary.
If I try to be too perfect, I get nervous.
I can't do it, but I've come to think of it as a way to grow and develop.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've had that experience.
It's a little bit easier, isn't it?
It's a little bit easier.
Hearing what Mr. Danbara just said
I feel like that was my turning point.
I think it's a turning point for me, to admit to myself that I can't do something.
I don't give up on myself for not being able to do something.
I'm not going to give up on myself for not being able to do something, but I'm going to accept the fact that I can't do something as a process.
I'll be more happy when I can do it.
And because you can see the whole process, you can enjoy our work.
I hope you can enjoy our work including that.
Yes, I do.
You can choose.
Please choose.
What do you think?
I know it's difficult, but it's fun.
It's fun, it's fun, it's fun, so what should I do?
I don't know.
I started this job because I wanted to make people smile and cheer them up.
I want to provide my fans with a place where they can have a lot of fun and enjoy themselves.
I hope that I can continue to do activities that make people excited.
I would like to do my best as an individual as well as in a group.
I've had the opportunity to do a solo concert called "Lulu Barat".
I was given the opportunity to do a solo concert called Lulu Barat, and I'm hoping to expand on that as well.
But group activities are also very interesting, so I'd like to enjoy those as well.
I hope I can use what I learned there in my own activities
I'd like to be able to use what I learn from the group in my own activities and do various things.
I'm a bit greedy, but I think it's okay to be greedy.
I don't know if it's okay for me to be greedy.
I see.
But I've only been a member for three years, about three years.
I'm still trying to raise myself up a little bit more.
I feel that I can grow a little more.
Like Mr. Dambara.
I've been watching Mr. Danbara.
I think she sings and performs in a way that draws you into the atmosphere of the song and the world of the song.
The other day at the Hina Festival, I felt like I was being swallowed up into the worldview of the song.
I want to perform while respecting the worldview of the song.
But I still don't know at all.
That's right.
I can still see my issues and problems.
I can see it.
It's the opposite, it's a time when it's becoming more noticeable.
I'm probably going through the period that Danmura-san was talking about earlier.
Oh, yes, that's true.
I think we will be going through it more and more from now on.
I hope I will be stronger when that happens.
I am able to put my feelings into my songs by making the most of my experiences.
Yes, but I think that's a big part of it.
I think so.
Life experiences come out in many things.
It's great that your songs also show your personality.
That's right.
I can tell what kind of person you are.
I can tell when I see you, Yumi.
Really?
That's great, but I want you to do your best.
And if you run into any problems, please tell me.
I really felt like I wanted to talk to you about something after talking to you today.
I'd love to talk to you about it.
Yes, maybe...
I may ask you for advice.
I'm looking forward to talking to you.
I look forward to working with you in the future.
Thank you very much.
Now, we have talked a lot so far, but I have written on this board some of the things that impressed me during our talk.
I don't seek perfection.
Yumi said, "I don't seek perfection.
But this is not a compromise.
Yes, it is.
I'm doing the best I can right now.
The part of you that can't do it, and the part of you that can do it.
You are who you are, and you should accept that.
You don't have to do it too perfectly.
That's what made me feel at ease.
I felt empathy for her.
This left a deep impression on me.
Thank you very much.
I sing with my face.
Because Danbara-san said this, it was really convincing
It was very convincing.
When I saw your solo performance at Hello Project Day Festival 2024
I saw your solo performance
I saw her solo performance at Hello Project Hibi no Fes 2024.
At that time, I watched a lot of Danbara's
I've been watching a lot of videos
I've been watching a lot of videos of Danbara's live performance
When I was pulled out of the screen
When I was pulled out on the screen
I matched it to the music.
I mean, you know, in tune with the music.
I think that's how their facial expressions
It's natural.
When he was in pain, he sang in a really painful voice.
And your facial expression...
I haven't been able to do that yet.
It's a point that I admire a lot.
And when Danbara-san says it, it's very convincing.
I thought it was very convincing
I thought it was wonderful.
that's why I chose this one.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to leave you with a picture of what we said to each other.
I'd like to leave a picture of what we said to each other.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
Here we go. 321.
It's done. It's done.
I was really concentrating on what I was listening to.
I mean, the floor project members are all really hard workers.
As you said, we all strive for perfection.
We all want perfection all at once, and that's exactly what you said.
Yumi Kasai's Sad Heaven... she's practicing all the time.
She sang backstage and offstage until the very last minute.
I saw that, so I was more moved by what you just said.
But every time you sang, you definitely grew up.
I was so happy to see that.
I was also very happy to hear that you had such feelings for her.
When Mr. Danbara started talking about the weather, he said, "There are many kinds of weather.
When Mr. Danbara started talking about the weather, he said, "There are many kinds of weather," and I really empathized with that.
I really empathized with that, and as I watched the video, I wondered where my own weather was.
I was thinking about what my own weather was while watching this video.
There are so many, it's hard to decide.
I can't make up my mind... I can't make up my mind.
I've heard other people's songs.
I can't make up my mind... I mean, I look at the images of myself singing every day... and listen to other people's songs.
I can't make up my mind... I can't make up my mind.
I think that each member is thinking a lot about how to sing next time.
I can't make up my mind.
I think that each time I see you, your singing style is evolving so much.
There are many members who are evolving their singing style every time I see them.
I was really impressed by the fact that everyone is really thinking about various things when they sing.
I was very impressed.
That's all for now.
I'm sure you'll be fine as usual!
Here is the next one!
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 Making Movie
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 was held at Makuhari Messe on March 30 and 31.
Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 was held at Makuhari Messe on March 30th and 31st, featuring the solo and shuffle units.
Please have a look!
We look forward to seeing you soon!
E-ru-hai!
Rather than doing the shoulders like this, I'm going to do the body like this.
like this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
you want to be a heroine?
YOU KEEP
Hey...
I was told by the members that Riai would be a winner, so I was allowed to enter Niien as well.
Last year, Ikuta-san told me that Riai Matsunaga would win if she could.
I had a feeling that I would be right this year, so when I was right, I thought, "I knew it.
I was really looking forward to working hard in the shuffle corner because it was a rare opportunity to meet the members of the team.
I wasn't present at the time of the drawing, so the leader, Mr. Kamikuro Ryu, drew in my place.
I didn't hear from him, and I was surprised when I heard from Akako that she was on the same team with Akani.
It was my first time to win the shuffle, so I'm going to do my best.
For the first time
I didn't even expect to win, so I was really surprised.
It's the first time for me to be in a group with this many people, so I'm really looking forward to it!
me
The updates are cheerful, so I'm just looking forward to having fun.
I hope it will be a lot of fun.
I'm going to be a heroine.
It's my first time to win.
So I'm nervous, but I hope I can enjoy it.
I will do my best.
Thank you for watching.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. A wonderful future.
You see, everyone is longing for
Terrible.
This was the first day of the festival since the ban on vocal performances was lifted, so the audience was very energetic,
Every time we started a song, they would say "whoa," so I was really excited too.
It was fun.
I was too nervous.
I didn't realize how nervous I was.
I think I was really nervous.
My face was stiff.
But it was the first shuffle in two years,
I was the top one,
I felt a little responsible,
But we were all quite young,
I was energized by everyone's energy,
I think I was able to enjoy it without being too nervous.
You were very cool.
It was really cool.
He really was.
I have been wanting you to sing the song "Narojo-no-kara" (Let's be Heroines) for a long time,
I had requested him to sing a song called "Let's be this heroine" at birthday events and so on,
But due to some circumstances, that request was not granted, and that's how I ended up performing this time at the "imit" event,
I was very happy to see what I really wanted to see,
I was very happy to see what I really wanted to see.
Of course, Matsumura-san was really cool, and Akiyama-san, too.
You were so cool.
And Akiyama-san was really cool, too,
I was really, really happy to see the difference in performance because of the different groups,
I was very happy to see the difference in performance because of the different groups.
It is true that Tinafest is a one-time event.
That's right.
So there is a strange sense of tension, and it is because it is only one time,
We want to show how cool we are, and there are a lot of feelings involved in performing on stage,
We all had many feelings on stage, but all of us had already finished our parts,
I think it was really cool to see that, and I think the shuffle was really cool,
I think it was really cool to see that,
I think each member has various feelings such as, "Oh, I'm the senior, I should be in charge.
I think each member has various feelings.
I think each member has his/her own thoughts and feelings about it,
It was really cool.
That's all for now. Project Tinafest 2024 making video.
Thank you for your work!
Reina Yokoyama of Morning Musume。 24 and
Rin Kono of Angelem are presenting this apkami.
Here is the next one!
Tsubaki Factory Power Flower
Now is the time to be a single eye! Vocal Recording
From Tsubaki Factory's latest album
Power Flower: Now is the time to be an eye!
Please take a look at the vocal recording of Yof Luno!
We are waiting for you!
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Then let's begin.
Yes, sir.
Let's begin.
The signal for the beginning is sweetly rising
A story modest but proudly hidden
The year of the red bloom, brought back tight
To a brightness that stands out
Days
The way you sing is cool.
The rhythm could be a little snappier
I'd like to make the rhythm a little snappier, but I think I'm going to accentuate it a little more firmly.
Thank you for watching!
The beginning is signalled by a coarse rise.
A modest gesture, but with a hidden interest
The year of the red bloom, brought back tight
to an eye-catching vividness
Still image
I'd like to try one.
I'd like to try one of these.
I'd like to try a little more deformation.
"Cue the beginning." Roughly up.
Cool, you mean?
Yeah, yeah, cool.
Roughly up.
Yes, yes, with a little emphasis.
Girly.
Cue smiley face. Roughly up.
OK, let's try it after that
Take 1
Take 2
Yeah, let's go over that a little bit too.
Yes, perfect.
Mental training is a little hard to say.
Spiritual practice.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Let's get it right.
Okay, let's go with that.
The unprecedented amount was a little loose. You've got to be strong there, too.
You don't have to be a cancer.
But I'm going to accentuate it a little bit. That's about right.
All Humanity and Elvasing Gandaby Online
OK, let's continue.
Elvasing Gundaby Online
Tsubaki HanamichiDecorating everything is all right
The overlapping power is facing the blue sky
The figure is dignified, graceful and beautiful
All over the world
Beautiful is a little fargin
Beautiful
Let's go a little lighter.
Here.
Let's make it a little beautiful... but not too beautiful... but not too beautiful.
The overlapping forces are going for the blue sky.
A little breezy.
I think it's better to sing a little lighter.
I'll just take the overlapping power.
Yes, sir.
The overlapping power is...
Blue sky
Shall we sing until it's blue?
Yes
Hanami chi Hanami chi Hanami chi Hanami chi Hanami chi
Everything's all right
The overlapping forces are
Blue sky
Yeah, OK
Next, the first chorus
The figure is dignified
Graceful and beautiful
I want to look for it all over the world
I can't decorate my dream alone
Redder and redder
I want to keep shining on you
Kanae de naku naku na shimashita shimashita go shimashita shimashita
Kanae-ra
Yeah, yeah, yeah, let's go straight
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'd like to stop it once.
Root, your ah...
Higher and higher
I want to keep shining redder and redder
I'd like to keep going there
me
Hmm...
Well, let's continue.
Power Flower
Now is the time to work as one
We're moving forward together
To a place you've never seen before
Power Flower
power flower
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you gotta get the back of it.
Power Flower
You've got to get the power flower on the back side.
Okay, one more time.
Keep the red light shining on you
Now it's time to come together as one
We're moving forward together
To a place you've never seen before
Power flower
Now is the time to come together
♪ We're moving forward together
We're moving forward as one
To a place you've never seen
Power Flower
Okay, we're done.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
It was really cool. It was like seeing a different YOFU.
I was very happy to see a different YOFU, but when I see the vocal recording on the cardboard, I always think...
I'm always impressed by the director's ability to take what he says and transform it into something that I can immediately hear in my voice.
I was really impressed by the way he could take what he was told by the director and translate it into his own voice right away.
I was told to exaggerate it a bit more, and I was able to do it in my own way right away.
I'm always amazed when I watch vocal recordings, because everyone does it in a normal way, but it's honestly amazing that they do it in a normal way.
Yes, you're right. You've got your own habits, your own way of doing things.
Yes.
I think it's hard to get rid of your own habits and the way you used to sing, but Renochan was able to listen immediately and express them in her singing.
That's all for now, Tsubaki Factory Power Flower, now is the time to unite as one! This was YOFU Runo's vocal recording.
Let's do our best again tomorrow!
This is Reina Yokoyama and Rin Kono, and it's time to say goodbye to Apkami!
Well, we've seen a lot of images this time, but I, Kono, would like to introduce you to a new corner, the Apkami Photo Gallery.
I, Kono, was very impressed with the new Apkami Photo Gallery section.
I was really impressed by the new section "Apkami Photo Gallery" where they talked about the turning point of their songs, and I thought it was very interesting.
I think it was a topic that the members themselves don't often have a chance to talk about, so I was very happy to be able to tell you about it here.
I'm very happy to be able to share it with you here.
And I, Kawayama, watched the video of HinaFest for the first time in a while and thought it was really cool.
After I said I hated it, I thought I should rewatch my own HinaFest video again.
It brought back so many memories for me.
It was so cool to see the cool footage.
I think I was shown some very cool videos.
In this article, we're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Please subscribe to our channel and we'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally see.
This time, our partners in the Apkami are Reina Yokoyama of Morning Musume 24 and Rin Kono of Angelum!
Good bye!
Next time on Apkami: JuiceJuice Tokyo Bras: Making of the Music Brio Shooting!
And we will be showing the behind-the-scenes of Hello Project Hina Fest 2024!
me